let's see family I'm looking for a place
a ver familia Estoy buscando un sitio
to tell you this gossip You're going to freak out well there you
para contaros este chisme Vais a flipar
have the title a bit I'll be
pues ahí tenéis un poco el título me
able to lie down here I'll tell you the gossip
podré echar yo aquí os cuento el chisme
bye
chao
[Music] I'm going to
[Música]
put on my glasses to go more to the
me voy a poner las gafas para ir más al
divine game Beachy gossip I'm going
juego divino salseo Playero me pongo sin
shirtless already beach plan no no no no no
camiseta ya en plan playa no no no no no
the physical change still nothing to
el cambio físico todavía nada para
show off so much a live lying on the
presumido tanto un directo tumbado en la
sand and me in an armchair I do what I
arena y yo en un sillón hago lo que
can JJ to bring you the gossip I
puedo JJ para traeros el chisme Yo
hope it doesn't get too echoed let's go the
espero que no se haga mucho eco vamos el
other day It was you Frank Cuesta's live show
otro día Fuiste tú el directo de Frank
they put it on channel 4 but by the
cuesta lo pusieron en la 4 pero by the
face just when I arrived on Monday I
face justo cuando llegué el lunes me
got a notification from YouTube that the
llegó una notificación de YouTube que el
great program I did with Frank
pedazo de programa que hice con Frank
Cuesta they put an
cuesta le pusieron una restricción de
age restriction on the video the video the Graphic went
edad al vídeo el vídeo la Gráfica iba
like
así y cuando le pone una restricción de
this and when they put an age restriction apart from the fact that it wasn't monetized it hits the Graphic a tremendous blow like boom it loads it But anyway what I do ask you is the same thing I asked you this morning okay go into the reupload but in  Instead of having a hundred and something thousand
pero en vez de tener ciento y pico mil
views, it has 40 or 50,000 views,
visitas pues tiene 40 o 50.000 visitas
share it and like it and give it
lo compartáis y le deis like y le deis
a lot of comments Marta, I'm taking a risk Marta, I'm taking a
muchos comentarios Marta arriesgo Marta
risk Marta is a bit of a
arriesgo Marta es una persona un poco
difficult person, she's a person who sometimes
difícil es una persona que hay veces que
when you say something she doesn't like or you
cuando dices algo que no le gusta o le
contradict her, she's not very assertive,
llevas la contraria es poco asertiva
let's call it that We've put it in, we've
vamos a llamarlo así Eso lo hemos metido
experienced it okay
eso lo hemos vivido vale
[Music]
[Música]
today she's not going to like this live show,
hoy no le va a gustar este directo
obviously I'm not going to disrespect her
evidentemente no le voy a faltar respeto
and I'm still on her side in
y sigo estando al lado de ella en
some things and not in others, like with
algunas cosas y en otras no como con
anything goes But in the end, this information reaches me
todo vale Pero al final me llega esta
and obviously after
información y evidentemente después de
having verified it, I have to give it at
haberla contrastado la tengo que dar en
work, for me the headline would be very
mi trabajo para mí el titular sería muy
simple if she gets it after this news, she'll mess it up
sencillo si coge después de esta noticia
and block me and yell at me or
me la lía y me bloquea y me chilla o me
well, we're not that close, well, we
bueno no estamos tan cerca bueno el
already know about Marta's situation but
pronto de Marta ya lo sabemos pero
regardless of that, I'm telling you that
independientemente de eso ya os digo que
this information started reaching me
esta información me empieza a llegar de
a couple of days ago and I've been
hace un par de días y yo he estado
collecting things so I can tell it or
recopilando cosas para poder contarlo o
not If I couldn't  tell it because there wouldn't be
no Si yo no pudiera contarlo porque no
enough Well, I'll tell you
lo hubiera suficiente Pues nos lo cuento
but the truth is, I think it's that there is a
pero es que la verdad yo creo que es que
tomato today this morning it came to me
hay tomate hoy esta mañana me ha llegado
that Antonio David has felt hurt
que Antonio David se ha sentido dolido
with this information that has reached him
con esta información que le ha llegado
also I believe from what they tell me, he has been
también creo por lo que me cuentan pues
hurt because this could be
ha estado dolido porque esto se podría
considered disloyalty, you are the one who is
considerar una deslealtad el ti es el
this would be disloyalty because it
que es esto sería una deslealtad porque
is news and it is information that
es una noticia y es una información que
Marta laughs with her moment denied but of course
Marta ríe con su momento negó pero claro
if Marta with that moment had told
si Marta con ese momento hubiera dicho
the truth this data that we have would
la verdad estos datos que tenemos pues
not fit I am talking about Diego, a
no cuadraría estoy hablando de Diego
contestant on the island of temptations
concursante de la isla de la tentaciones
and recently a contestant on survivor
y hace poco concursante de superviviente
in 2021 Although the news comes out in
en el 2021 Aunque la noticia sale en
2022 and Marta denies it in 2021 Marta
2022 y Marta la niega en el 2021 Marta
riosco and Diego meet because of the issue of
riosco y Diego se conocen por el tema de
custody of the dog Marta goes to his house
la custodia del perro Marta va a su casa
does an interview and apparently
le hace una entrevista y al parecer
immediately there is a brutal feeling between
inmediatamente hay un feeling entre
them so much so that they meet more
ellos brutal tanto es así que quedan más
times I already know what they did when they
veces yo ya lo que hicieron cuando
met I cannot tell you I was not there
quedaron no lo puedo contar yo no estaba
but from what they tell me if what they
pero por lo que me cuentan si fuera
tell me was true  Well in
verdad lo que me cuentan Pues en este
2021 on the occasions when they meet they
2021 en las ocasiones en las que quedan
remain very hidden of course, which surprises
quedan como muy escondidas claro cosa
Diego because he does
que a Diego pues le sorprende porque él
not have to hide from meeting
no se tiene que esconder de quedar con
anyone today we know that Marta took a risk and
nadie hoy sabemos que Marta arriesgo y
Antonio David through Marta's mouth
Antonio David por la boca de Marta
risked three years of relationship so of course
arriesgo tres años de relación entonces
there would perhaps be the
pues claro ahí estaría tal vez la
explanation why they would have to
explicación por la que tendrían que
meet in a shopping center
quedar en un centro comercial a
secretly anyway Diego does not tell those things
escondidas en fin esas movidas no Diego
eh Diego then he goes on a reality show and
lo cuenta eh Diego luego va un reality y
tells it in fact I have the audio here I
lo cuenta de hecho tengo aquí el audio
put it for you as Diego tells it What do you
os lo pongo como Diego lo cuenta Qué
do alone but you live at risk
haces el solitario pero vives con riesgo
some girl like what has
alguna chica en plan rollo de que te ha
given you With all the noses of
dado Con tanto las narices de
normally I go out to party with my
normalmente yo salgo de fiesta con los
friends
colegas
a story at the time
una historia en su momento
that came to me from I don't know what
que a mí me llegó de no sé qué de que
that you were going to do a montage with Marta López with me she came to my house in León when I lived there for an interview about the music that had released I was with Horus and so on and then I talked a lot Antonio David spoke to me in Los Reyes
Antonio David me habló en Los Reyes
previous
anteriores
points and all that and then I met her
puntos y todo eso y luego quedé con ella
when all the commotion was
cuando estaba todo el revuelo
I had too much
que me sobraba
[Music]
[Música]
honestly I don't like it either, I
sinceramente a mí no me gusta tampoco no
'm not I mean I think you know there was an end
soy O sea yo creo que sabes había fin
here I have
aquí tengo
Antonio
Antonio
matures also
madura además
a direct proposal of something or not
una propuesta directa de algo o no
those things let's see I don't know well he
esas cosas a ver no sé
answered me stories when he
pues me respondía historias cuando
was on vacation in Marbella or
estuvo de vacaciones en Marbella o
Malaga in the summer of 2021 he also
Málaga el verano del 2021 también me
told me let's see if you have a few days here I do
dijo a ver si tienes por aquí unos días
n't think You know of course I don't know always in the
No creo Sabes claro Yo no sé siempre en
summer
verano
to talk about climate change
a hablar del cambio climático
[Music] let's
[Música]
see It turns out that when they
a ver Resulta ser que ellos cuando
meet so that Marta can do an
quedan para que Marta le haga una
interview about the custody issue
entrevista por el tema de la custodia
of Diego's dog I read that he has with
del perro de Diego la leo que tiene con
Lola and they have a feeling between them they have a
Lola y tienen un feeling entre ellos
nice roll there is feeling
tienen un rollete guapo hay feeling
between them there is chemistry let's say I think
entre ellos hay química digamos creo que
nothing happens there What happens is that
ahí no pasa nada Lo que pasa es que
then they follow each other on social media and in one
luego ellos se siguen en redes y en una
of these Diego says he's going to
de estas Que Diego dice que va a ir a
buy the kings Marta tells him Hey well
comprar los reyes Marta le dice Oye pues
I also have to go buy the
yo también tengo que ir a comprar los
kings we meet and they meet secretly in
reyes quedamos y quedan a escondidas en
a shopping center in fact Marta
un centro comercial de hecho Marta Le
explains to him how they have to do it so that they do
explica cómo tienen que hacerlo para que
n't get caught and to meet and I don't know what
no les pillen y para quedar y no sé qué
clear here the move would be the following
claro aquí la movida sería la siguiente
that Marta  risk in 2021 he went to
que Marta riesgo en el 2021 se fue a
buy the kings twice because he
comprar los reyes dos veces porque
also went to buy the kings not this
también fue a comprar los reyes no esta
story When Diego tells it in
historia Cuando Diego lo cuenta en el
2022 Marta denies it but not only does he
2022 Marta lo niega pero no solamente lo
deny it but Marta denies it
niega sino que Marta lo niega
publicly Antonio David denies it
públicamente se lo niega Antonio David
because of course Then let's warn kea
porque claro Entonces avisemos kea
because the date coincides with him yes it
porque la fecha coinciden con él sí que
is true that she would
es verdad que
meet Diego in the middle of some
quedaría con Diego en mitad de algunos
fights since the Barbie and
mosquillos desde la parejita de Barbie
Ken couple I don't remember but there was anger
de Ken no me acuerdo pero hubo mosqueo
not one of these fights that they
no de unos mosqueos de estos que
had and there Marta met Diego
tuvieron y por ahí Marta quedó con Diego
the question is the following Marta gets
la cuestión es la siguiente Marta se
very angry I don't know how you can
enfada mucho yo no sé cómo me puedes
do this to me because of how well we have
hacer esto por lo bien que nos hemos
gotten along because of how much we like each other I don't know
llevado por lo bien que nos caemos no sé
what and I have in my possession a video that
qué y tengo en mi poder un vídeo que
Of course you see This video and you say how she
Claro tú ves Este vídeo y dices tú cómo
does This video if Marta got angry with
hace Este vídeo si Marta se enfado con
Diego
Diego
loves
amores
loves that kill
amores que matan
Andy Andy come on Come on come on Come on olé this
Andy Andy ande Ande ande Ande olé esto
is a private room a nightclub these little
es un reservado una discoteca estas
hands here these little hands with a
manitas aquí estas manitas con un
blue dress you see those legs with a
vestido azul veis esas piernas con un
blue dress that leg with a blue dress
vestido azul esa pierna con un vestido
and next to her was  Diego doesn't seem very
y al lado estaba Diego no parece muy
angry right Emilio of course he doesn't seem
enfadado verdad Emilio claro no parece
very angry this was recently and I'm going
muy enfadado esto es hace poco y os voy
to tell you something that I want you to
a decir una cosa que quiero que ustedes
check because I'm on vacation right now
comprobéis porque yo ahora estoy de
and I don't feel like it this video
vacaciones y no tengo ganas este vídeo
that I just put up belongs to the
que os acabo de poner pertenece a la
night of May 16th to 17th of this year
noche del 16 al 17 de mayo de este año
Now I want my lordship and my
Ahora yo quiero que mi señoría y mi
kids to look for the date to see the
chavalería busquéis la fecha a ver las
stories they can't be recovered on
historias no se pueden recuperar
Instagram but now I want my
Instagram pero ahora yo quiero que mis
kids and my lordship to check
chavalería y mi señoría revisen
reactions on YouTube because luckily
reacciones en YouTube porque por suerte
or unfortunately there are many channels
o por desgracia Pues hay muchos canales
on YouTube where we comment on things that
en YouTube que comentamos las cosas que
celebrities do in their
hacen los famosos en sus historias de
Instagram stories I hope there aren't any
Instagram Espero que no haya ninguna
Instagram stories during those days in
historia de Instagram en esos días de
May it's like Marta was crying taking
Mayo es lo que Marta estuviera llorando
out the love book Zero because the
sacando el libro de amor Zero porque la
truth is it would be a disappointment I'm not
verdad sería una decepción que no te
telling you if it doesn't come out Damn but I'm not taking
digo que no salga [__] pero no me esté
out a little book love zero and you
sacando un librito amor cero y te lo
're passing it on too May 16th to 17th
estés pasando también 16 al 17 de mayo
Diego does not live in Madrid this day Diego was
Diego no vive en Madrid este día Diego
coming from recording the
venía de grabar el debate de
survivors debate you know that the
supervivientes ya sabéis que el debate
final debate is recorded it's not a debate
final se graba no es un debate en
live and this is after recording the
directo y esto es después de grabar el
debate because there is a private room and
debate pues queda se va un reservado y
Marta stays with them according to
Marta queda con ellos según Me comentan
my sources more than one source more than two
mis Fuentes más de una fuente más de dos
sources according to what they tell me when
Fuentes según Me comentan cuando todo el
everyone leaves when everyone I
mundo se va cuando todo el mundo me
mean when the group that is in the club
refiero cuando el grupo que está en la
in the private room leaves because they are
discoteca en el reservado se va porque
more there with friends and so on Marta and
está más ahí con amigos y demás Marta y
Diego stay there I can't say what I
Diego se quedan ahí yo no puedo decir lo
want or rather I wasn't there what I
que quiero o sea yo no estaba allí yo lo
know is that they were there that they
que sé es que estaban allí que se
stayed there and two sources confirm this to me
quedaron allí y me lo confirman dos
not three sources that have
Fuentes no tres Fuentes que no tienen
nothing to do with each other I have
nada que ver la una con la otra Yo he
been trying to investigate a little
estado intentando Investigar un poquito
and I have the following this photo of Diego
y tengo lo siguiente esta foto de Diego
from May 17th at the hotel where he
del 17 de mayo en el hotel donde
was in Madrid but if you notice
estuviera de Madrid pero si os fijáis
there is a like from Marta risk therefore there
hay un like de Marta riesgo por lo tanto
are people who are pointing out to me that in the
hay gente que me está señalando que al
background there is a Sara bag but
fondo de la hay una bolsa del Sara pero
of course here already
claro aquí ya
here Of course but for me that there is a
aquí Claro pero para mí que haya una
bag of the tsar in the back doesn't mean
bolsa del zar atrás tampoco significa
anything you know that would be ideal to touch
nada sabéis que sería lo ideal tocar a
me that there is a Sara bag it doesn't tell me
mí que hay una bolsa del Sara no me dice
anything a Sara bag put on because yes
nada una bolsa del Sara puesta porque sí
there are men's clothes too  there what would be
hay ropa de hombre también ahí lo que
the [ __ ] the [ __ ] the [ __ ] that
sería la [__] la [__] la [__] que
you would find would be the 17th if Marta
encontrarais sería el día 17 si Marta
risked she was dressed as Sara If
arriesgó iba vestida del Sara Si
you find that you are let's go Sherlock
encontráis eso sois vamos Sherlock
Holmes that happens on the 17th at night okay
Holmes eso pasa el 17 por la noche vale
this I just told it happens on the 17th at
esto acabo de contar pasa el 17 por la
night and on the 18th Marta then
noche y el 18 Marta entonces dominio
public domain obviously Because everything is
público evidentemente Porque todo lo va
uploaded by Instagram Marta is going to Menorca
subiendo Instagram Marta se va a menorca
with her friends and according to several people
con las amigas y según varias personas
several each on their own have been
varias cada una por su lado han ido
telling others Diego and Marta have
contando a otras Diego y Marta tienen
a disagreement Marta asks Diego to
un desencuentro Marta le pide a Diego
meet him when he returns from Menorca
quedar con él cuando regrese de menorca
and Diego tells him no Marta gives him a
y Diego le dice que no Marta le monta un
hell of a fight And now I'll tell you a
pitote de la [__] Y ahora os cuento un
fact that must be added to this moment
dato que hay que Añadir a este momento
of the fight but to tell you this I
de la bronca pero para contaros esto
have to do the croquette on the ground
tengo que hacer la croqueta en el suelo
of the beach it has to be done
de la playa es que hay que hacerlo
when I tell you You're going to understand
cuando os lo cuente lo Vais a entender
Antonio David was also talking on the
Antonio David estaba hablando por
phone with Marta through her
teléfono también con Marta a través del
friend's cell phone Marta risks
móvil de la amiga Marta arriesgo se
being fighting with Diego over one
estaba peleando con Diego por un
phone and with Antonio David over another
teléfono y con Antonio David por otro
Marta  I risk while I was in
Marta arriesgo mientras que estaba en
Menorca she was fighting with Antonio
menorca se estaba peleando con Antonio
David on the phone and on the other
David por teléfono y por el otro
phone with Diego but at the
teléfono con el Diego pero en estos
moment and with this I'll tell you this
momentos y ya con esto os cuento esto
last thing and then I'll put the
último y ya después ya le pongo el
finishing touches on it and I'm leaving I don't know for how long but you can
broche y me voy no sé hasta cuándo pero
leave me alone right now
ya me dejáis en paz en estos momentos no
they're not so bad because Marta
están tan mal porque pues porque Marta
risked
arriesgó ha subido este fin de semana
uploaded a photo this weekend of her on a motorcycle and Jane
una fotito subida en una moto y Jane
Lover who is a Latin lovers
Lover que es un Latin lovers a Diego le
made the following comment to Diego I'm
ha puesto el siguiente comentario os lo
going to read it to you okay Jane lovers to Marta's photo
voy a leer vale Jane lovers a la foto de
she puts a heart face in her
Marta le pone carita de corazón en los
eyes but Marta risk
ojos pero es que Marta riesgo le
answers the comment and says James
contesta el comentario y le pone James
Lover I'm taking you
Lover te llevo
to put the finishing touches on this
para ponerle el broche a esta
information
información
here it's not going to be heard here no wait I'll be
aquí no se va a escuchar aquí no espera
back
vuelvo
Oh I left my flip-flop there where I was
Ay La chancla me la dejaba allí donde
recording I have to go there and I
estaba grabando tengo que ir para allá y
also left my glasses there
las gafas también las he dejado allí a
today Camila chuza would also
día de hoy Camila chuza también le
be giving likes to James lovers
estaría dando likes A James lovers por
therefore Camila chuza approves of this
lo tanto Camila chuza aprueba esta
friendship or influencer relationship and as I
relación de amistad o de influencer y lo
said sharing the program with Frank
dicho compartir el programa con Frank
costs  from the other day and let's see if it can
cuesta del otro día y a ver si puede
continue to trend too, a
seguir se pone en tendencia también un
kiss family
beso familia
[Music]
[Música]